User.create(username: "riddler1313", email: "riddler1313@gmail.com", password: "1234")
User.create(username: "veronica_the_quizmaster", email: "vquizzer@yahoo.com", password: "abcd")
User.create(username: "horatio58", email: "horace.martin@me.com", password: "8675309")

Deck.create(name: "Eigth Grade Vocab", user_id: 1)
Deck.create(name: "US state capitals", user_id: 1)
Deck.create(name: "Shakespeare Villains", user_id: 2)
Deck.create(name: "Chemical symbols", user_id: 3)
Deck.create(name: "World Capitals", user_id: 3)

Card.create(front: "laudable", back: "deserving praise or commendation", deck_id: 1)
Card.create(front: "succinct", back: "briefly and clearly expressed", deck_id: 1)
Card.create(front: "robust", back: "strong and healthy; powerful", deck_id: 1)
Card.create(front: "nadir", back: "lowest point in fortunes", deck_id: 1)
Card.create(front: "intractable", back: "stubborn or hard to control", deck_id: 1)
Card.create(front: "impecunious", back: "having little or no money", deck_id: 1)

Card.create(front: "Pennsylvania", back: "Harrisburg", deck_id: 2)
Card.create(front: "Michigan", back: "Langsing", deck_id: 2)
Card.create(front: "Florida", back: "Tallahassee", deck_id: 2)
Card.create(front: "Minnesota", back: "Saint Paul", deck_id: 2)
Card.create(front: "New Jersey", back: "Trenton", deck_id: 2)
Card.create(front: "Wisconsin", back: "Madison", deck_id: 2)

Card.create(front: "Claudius", back: "Hamlet", deck_id: 3)
Card.create(front: "Macduff", back: "Macbeth", deck_id: 3)
Card.create(front: "Iago", back: "Othello", deck_id: 3)
Card.create(front: "Shylock", back: "Merchant of Venice", deck_id: 3)
Card.create(front: "Don John", back: "Much Ado About Nothing", deck_id: 3)
Card.create(front: "Tamora", back: "Titus Andronicus", deck_id: 3)

Card.create(front: "H", back: "Hydrogen", deck_id: 4)
Card.create(front: "Li", back: "Lithium", deck_id: 4)
Card.create(front: "Na", back: "Sodium", deck_id: 4)
Card.create(front: "K", back: "Potassium", deck_id: 4)
Card.create(front: "Mg", back: "Magnesium", deck_id: 4)
Card.create(front: "Ca", back: "Calcium", deck_id: 4)
Card.create(front: "Ti", back: "Titanium", deck_id: 4)

Card.create(front: "Afghanistan", back: "Kabul", deck_id: 5)
Card.create(front: "Albania", back: "Tirana", deck_id: 5)
Card.create(front: "Algeria", back: "Algiers", deck_id: 5)
Card.create(front: "Andorra", back: "Andorra la Vella", deck_id: 5)
Card.create(front: "Angola", back: "Luanda", deck_id: 5)
Card.create(front: "Argentina", back: "Buenos Aires", deck_id: 5)
Card.create(front: "Armenia", back: "Yerevan", deck_id: 5)

